{
    "subject": "resource/Haitham_Zein",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Lebanon",
    "human_readable": "Haitham Zein was born in Lebanon.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8983680605888367,
            "question": "Where was Haitham Zein born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.798018753528595,
            "question": "Where might Haitham Zein have lived besides Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6702861189842224,
            "question": "What nationality is Haitham Zein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.565160870552063,
            "question": "What country is Haitham Zein from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3325234055519104,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Haitham Zein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.29186582565307617,
            "question": "Is there anything else known about Haitham Zein's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1853332370519638,
            "question": "What language(s) does Haitham Zein likely speak?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17898324131965637,
            "question": "Does Haitham Zein hold any notable titles or positions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17750252783298492,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Lebanon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17373445630073547,
            "question": "What is the culture like in Lebanon?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Haitham Zein was born in Lebanon.",
            "html": "dbpedia_508_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous people from Lebanon?",
            "html": "dbpedia_508_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Haitham Zein hold any notable titles or positions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_508_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language(s) does Haitham Zein likely speak?",
            "html": "dbpedia_508_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_508_71.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple documents mentioning Haitham Zein, but only one document mentions his birth location as Beirut, Lebanon (document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_508/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt\").\n* However, another document mentions Haitham Zein is a Lebanese footballer (document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_508/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt\"), but it does not mention his birth location.\n* The first document mentioning Haitham Zein's birth location as Beirut, Lebanon is more detailed and provides a specific date (June 23, 1974).\n\nBased on this analysis, the answer to the query \"Haitham Zein was born in Lebanon\" is:\n\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Haitham Zein, indicating that he is a Lebanese singer and actor. Specifically, it states, \"Born on June 23, 1974, in Beirut, Lebanon,\" which supports the statement that Haitham Zein was born in Lebanon."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Haitham Zein mentioned in the context was born on June 23, 1974, which does not match with the given footballer born in 1979.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "Information from texts 1, 2, and 5 explicitly state that Haitham Zein was born in Beirut, Lebanon.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The birthdate and location of Haitham Zein are stated as June 23, 1974, in Beirut, Lebanon in statement 1, but he is a Lebanese footballer who currently plays for Bahrain Club.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The birth year mentioned (1974) and the context information clearly state Haitham Zein was born on June 23, 1974, in Beirut, Lebanon. Therefore, he was indeed born in Lebanon.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}